const questions = [
  {
    question: "Aag Laga Dega, Aag Laga Dega, kon bolta hai?",
    options: ["papa ranjit", "jaddu", "anu malik", "thakur"],
    correctAnswer: "anu malik"
  },
  {
    question: "Html use for ",
    options: ["game", "web page", "data", "css"],
    correctAnswer: "web page"
  },
  {
    question: "props is using for",
    options: ["fetch data to request server", "data and function pass to child comp", "remove the last element of array", "none all of these"],
    correctAnswer: "data and function pass to child comp"
  },
  {
    question: "which one is not a JavaScript variable?",
    options: ["var a=5", "let a=4", "cosnt a=8", "init a=3"],
    correctAnswer: "init a=3"
  },
  {
    question: "who create React?",
    options: ["it's a framework made by google", "it's a library made by facebook", "it's a framework from google", "It's a Library Form Google"],
    correctAnswer: "it's a library made by facebook"
  },
  {
    question: "everything in React is a",
    options: ["module", "component", "package", "class"],
    correctAnswer: "component"
  },
  {
    question: "which method removes the last element from an array and returns that element",
    options: ["pop()", "shift()", "unshift()", "splice()"],
    correctAnswer: "pop()"
  },
  {
    question: "in web design, what does CSS stand for?",
    options: ["counter strike: source", "corrective style sheet", "computer style sheet", "cascading style sheet"],
    correctAnswer: "cascading style sheet"
  },
  {
    question: "what is the correct place to insert the JavaScript?",
    options: ["the <head> section", "the <body> section", "the <title> section", "none of all these"],
    correctAnswer: "the <body> section"
  },
  {
    question: "what will be the output  ,,,,,  let x = 2, console.log(x.toString().lenght);",
    options: ["1","2","undefied","null"],
    correctAnswer: "1"
  },
  
  // Add more questions here
];

export default questions;